

Ralph Pierre Rhode EXY

SUMMARY

Dedicated web developer, experienced in responsive web design and implementation. Strong creative, collaboration and problemsolving skills with an eye for detail. In conclusion, I am a prolific, full stack web developer with a high level passion.

- (+52) 753 213 7159
- 28, San León 626, Pedregal de Santa Úrsula, CDMX, Mexico
- rhodeexy@gmail.com
- https://jesuisunjerome.github.io/MyPortfolio/

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Technological University of Tehuacán, Puebla, Mexico Graduated with the highest grade in IT at the Technological University of Tehuacán

EXPERIENCES

2020 - Present

Estrategias en Tecnología de Información S.A

Web Designer, Full-stack web developer.

Freelance web developer

Designed an ecommerce web app (fully responsive). Building the ecommerce web app in order to increase the company sales.

2019 - 2020 Grupo Seguridad Integral – Web developer

Full-stack web developer responsible for web app development. Developed 7 web apps and designed more than 3. Boosted user experience and decrease rework.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

CSS3 / Bootstrap	HTML5	C# - Asp .Net
SQL server	Javascript	Figma
English	French	Spanish